Aarón Picó Pascual

Computer Engineer Artificial Intelligence Researcher







picoaaron@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/aaron-picopascual



https://aaron99p.github.io/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Artificial Intelligence Researcher

2022 - Present

VRAIN - UPV

University professor

2022 - Present

Universidad Politécnica de Valencia (UPV)

Data Science Engineer - Web Developer

2021 - 2022

Possible Inc

Computer Engineer

2020

Odyssey Robotics

EDUCATION

PhD in Computer Science (IA)

2022 - Present

VRAIN - Universidad Politécnica de Valencia (UPV)

Master in Artificial Intelligence,

Shape Recognition and Digital Image

2021 - 2022

Universidad Politécnica de Valencia (UPV)

Degree in Computer Engineering

2017 - 2021

Universidad de Alicante (UA)

PERSONAL PROFILE

Computer scientist specialized in AI

I am a **computer engineer** specialized in **Artificial Intelligence (AI)** with a strong academic background and a great passion for **research and innovation.**

I am currently conducting a <u>research that brings together</u> <u>the fields of AI and Psychology</u> to create systems that improve the mental and emotional well-being of users.

PROJECTS

- Emotion recognition with a smart wristband Poster
- Deep Learning Projects as Medical Image
 Classification
- Federated Learning
- Autonomous Robot Navigation

<u>Video 1</u> - <u>Video 2</u>

3D Mapping: Point CloudsVideo

More in http://personales.alumno.upv.es/apicpas/cv/aaron.html

SKILLS

- Attentive, observant and constant
- Versatile and self-taught
- **Teamwork**

LANGUAGES

- Spanish
- English
- Valencian / Catalan

COMPETENCES

- Programming: Python, C++, Java
- IA: Tensorflow, Keras, Pandas, Redes Neuronales
- Web development: Django, Vue.js, REST, Flask, Three.js

App development: Angular, Ionic, Unity Robotics/Electronics: ROS, Arduino

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB

